New day, new FWD product. Today,
Set for Life Plus. Set for Life Plus is
a VUL plan. It's an investment link
insurance plan that protects plus more.
And by the way, VUL stands for variable
unit link. VUL is also known as
insurance with investment component.
FWDL products like manifest, smart
start, and fast lane. Link description
box.
set for life. By the way, this is going
to be a long video, so please grab your
coffee or snack and just save this video
for later. So, let's get started
screen. So, benefits at a glance. Set
for life has life insurance protection.
So, set for life insurance investment
benefits like startup bonus, guaranteed
milestone increase, loyalty bonus, and
premium extension bonus. If you will
notice manifest set for life plus
options debt benefit. Number one is
level debt benefit. Number two is the
increasing debt benefit level increasing
debt
smart. Okay. When you say level FWD will
provide the value of whichever is higher
at the time of the insured's debt.
whichever is higher. Letter A 105% B
account value or letter B sum assured
Pak insurance no face amount life
insurance plus 125% of topups minus 125%
of withdrawals so whichever is higher
during the time of death
increasing debt benefit FWD will provide
the value of whichever is higher at the
time of the insured debt
so letter A5% of the account value so
letter Bured or the life insurance plus
the account value plus the 125% of top
ups less 125% of withdrawals
insurance
[Music]
investment focus
couple with kids
for example if you're a
That means insurance,
especially if this is your first
insurance plan.
By the way,
101 link in the description box. And of
course it is a set for life
or aggressive
first startups
[Music]
15% annual premium startup bonus 500k to
1 million 20% % over 1 million
25% basic premium startup bonus end of
year and 10th year
[Music]
and number two guaranteed milestone
increase
start
[Applause]
or retirement preapproved coverage
increase up to 20% coverage. So 20%
assured maximum is 2 million. And take
note, no medical needed increase
or life insurance. And you can redeem up
to 90 days from the milestone event as
long as insured is below 65 years old.
Financial planner.
Next is loyalty bonus. The longer you
stay with us, the more rewarding for
you. Get an additional 1% of your
average monthly account value on your
10th year and every 5 years after.
average value. So what
next is premium extension bonus.
will keep rewarding you with 2% for your
extensions. For examp
2% is 2,000 pesos extra for you
11 to 20th year.
So anyway,
other benefits set for life plus or SF
plus embedded rider which is accidental
debt coverage and waiver of premium.
Accidental debt if your beneficiaries
can get an additional cash benefit
should you pass away due to accident on
or before age 75. And they'll receive
three times the benefit if it happens on
a covered Philippine holiday. That
meansion
during a covered Philippine holiday for
example Christmas 1 million 3 million
pesos for your family. Next is waiver of
premium
waiver premium future premiums if ever
you are diagnosed with major critical
illness or permanent disability before
age 70. That means
cancer
remaining let's say second year
and then 10 years
remaining third to 10th year
because labor of premium set for life
plus this is to help you focus Focus on
your health and recovery
waiver of premiums
and give yourself for life plus
coverage. Even more of a plus factor
with an add-on benefits
riders like additional life insurance or
term insurance, additional
hospitalization per day, additional
critical illness coverage or rider
critical illness
amounts
for a critical illness
and hospital benefit. benefit recovery
proje,000
minimum premium minimum coverage amount
is 500% regular annual premium issue age
is 0 to 75 years
years old
as long as
[Music]
a 35 single marketing head at an online
shop company. Reza purchased FWD set for
life plus 5 years to pay with increasing
debt benefit. Nothing,000
basic premium,000
80,000,000
million coverage assured or life
insurance and then accidental debt
benefit 1.5 million and waiver premium
embedded. So premium is 88,754
critical illness rider
because of that.5 million
additional 300,000 coverage which is 1.8
8 million coverage
at no medical needed. She completed
paying for the 5year premium.
5 years into her plan,000
which is startup bonus 50%
another 50% on 5 years into her plan
10,000 was credited into her total
account value. This is the first 50% of
the startup bonus. Another 50%
44th
year plan. So maybe higher or lower
based on fund prices at time of
crediting.
By the way, if Riza is diagnosed with a
major critical illness or becomes
totally or permanently disabled, all
remaining premiums will be waved.
Critical illness plan
illness
42 major critical illness
premiums total and permanently disabled.
So option
critical illness
first major critical illness wave future
premiums
totally and permanently disabled
premium
of
Risa passes away due to an accident on
or before 75, her beneficiaries will get
the accident debt benefit or coverage of
1.5 million. So 64 Reza retired from
work. The withdrawal account value to
use as an additional source of
retirement income is look 4.4,4,469,354.
4 million4,469,354
pesos assuming fund growth rate of 8%.
4.4 4 million retirement 8% but again
this is not guaranteed
will depend on the actual fund
performance
and at 79 visa pass away and her
beneficiaries will receive the
14.5 million 14,553,15
pesos
benefit assuming growth rate again of 8%
imagine
[Music]
comment down below.
options.
Happy ending retirement
It's best to get life insurance while
you are young, healthy, and capable.
It's best to get it now. Okay. So,
another
congratulations
your financial planner. They will help
you.
Jeroes
Jeroy this time s Jero is a married man
with three kids finance director at a
real estate company. So sir Jericho
purchased an FWD set for life plus 10
years to pay with level debt benefit
coverage is 2 million pesos level
meaning whichever is higher you account
value or sum assured. So whichever
life insurance or debt benefit
is increasing so option letter A you
105% of the account value or letter B
some assured plus the account value so
insurance focus coverage is 2 million
pesos basic premium is 50,000 per year
is 80,000 so option 1 million accidental
debt coverage and waiver premiums total
premium Jero is 55,22 25.86 per year 45
Jericho received startup bonus 3,125
Jericho and his family purchased a new
house and applied
guaranteed milestone increase additional
400,000
coverage.
49.
He completed a 10ear premium period. But
let me just remind you
minimum paying period 5 years or 10
years minimum
value. Okay. So
value
again
50 years old on the 10 policy year he
received the 9375
remaining 75% startup bonus so startup
bonus 25% % and then 75% again meong
waiver of premium. So if Jerry diagnosed
with major critical illness or becomes
totally or permanently disabled, all
remaining premiums will be waved.
accidental benefit
due to an accident before age 75AD
for his premium and receives 1,000 as
premium extension bonus bring 1,000
pesos that is added to the total account
value.
Unfortunately, he was not able to pay
his premium extension that year. premium
extension.
So 57 to 59 Jericho has bounced back
from his financial problems and resume
paying for his premium. So he receives
1,000 for each payment made and 64
Jericho retired from work and the
withdrawal account value at the 25th
year is
2.5
million pesos which he can use as an
additional source of retirement income.
source of income especially for our
future self.
So make sure ready prepared
retirement
nightmare but holiday 84 Jericho he
passed away and his beneficiaries will
receive the 12.4 4 million life
insurance benefitable.
[Music]
Why not join my team?
I hope
leave it in the comment section. Share
this video to your friends, to your
besties, to your loved ones,
whatever happens. And also, you can join
my free Facebook community, Finance Glow
Bestie. By the way, hello. My name is
Fisha Bashal, your finance low bestie.
And let's grow and glow together.
[Music]